本字幕由YYeTs人人影视原创翻译制作
最新最快的美剧 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译： Glory  Nil  lighthouse  我是无辜哒
翻译： Requiem   校对：Glory  何何  非燕时间轴：雨中泪
■
你个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
你杀了我儿子
You're behind my son's death.
总统阁下
Madame president...
你丈夫在我手里
I have your husband.
下令让你的军队 从我的国家
You will have your forces Withdrawn from around my country,
桑加拉的边境永久撤军
Sangala,immediately and permanently.
否则你丈夫会被
Or your husband will die a slow
我只想确认一下
I just wanted to make sure
你今晚会不会回来吃饭
That youere still coming to dinner tonight.
抱歉  玛丽卡  我会补偿的
Marika,i can't. I'll make it up to you.
你要找玛丽卡的话  她不在我这
If you're looking for marika, she's not with me.
我找的是你  塞缪尔
I'm looking for you,samuel.
或许这不是你的真名
Or whatever your real name is.
我不想知道你的身份  也不在乎
Now,i don't know who you really are,and I don't care.
我只想让你远离我妹妹
I just want you out of my sister's life.
对一件事守口如瓶
Keep an incident quiet
直到我和杰克搞定一切
Until what jack and I are doing goes done.
沃斯勒死了
Vossler's dead.
杰克在里根街18号的酒店杀了他
Jack killed him at the hotel
他是正当防卫
On 18th and reagan. it was seldefense.
该死  蕾妮  你和他到底在干吗
Damn it,renee,what the hell are you doing with this guy?
我们应该抓捕疑犯  不是处决他们
You're supposed to bring suspects in, not murder them.
在我们查出杜巴库的内线之前
Until we know who dubaku's source is there,
你不能把这事告诉局里的人
You've got to hale this outside the bureau.
杜巴库是唯一知道在政府里面
Dubaku is the only person with the names of the people
都有谁背叛了您的人
Who betrayed you within your government
我们必须找到他
It's imperative that we find him.
你已经辞去了公职
You resigned from government service
参议院也把你定性为叛国者
and the senate regards you as having been a renegade agent.
这叫我如何相信你呢
How am I supposed to know where your loyalties really lie?
恕我直言  总统阁下
With all due respect, madame president,
您可以打听我的为人
Ask around.
我查到了亨利·泰勒的地址
I got an address for henry taylor.
快叫救护车
Get an ambulance!
以下事件发生于下午4点到5点
任何人都不许入内
No one else gets through here.
跟我来
Follow me.
他是亨利·泰勒  总统的丈夫
It'senryaylor, the esident's husband,
但别走漏风声  明白吗
But that information is not to be disseminated. clear?
我
I...
泰勒先生  请不要讲话
Mr. taylor,don't speak.
我需要您保存体力
I need you to save your energy.
在这
Over here!
抱歉  请后退
Excuse me. step back,please.
这是第6单元
This is unit six.
我这有一名胸部中枪的伤者
We have a gunshot trauma to the chest...
伤口直径9毫米
Nine-millimeter round.
胸骨下方9毫米伤口
Nine- millimeter substernal.
-脉搏跳动加速  -你没事吧
Pulse is rapid. are you okay?
-没事  -我要打电话给总统
Yeah. I'm gonna call the president.
我要你搜索全部房间
I want you to search all the rooms,see if you can get
看能否找到关于
Anything off their hardware
杜巴库去向的线索
That's going to tell us where dubaku went.
我是杰克·鲍尔
This is jack bauer.
我要和总统通话
I need to speak with the president.
请稍等
Hold one moment,please.
总统阁下
Madame president,
请您不要灰心丧气
I would encourage you not to lose hope.
杜巴库知道我们骗了他  伊桑
Dubaku knows we tried to deceive him, ethan.
他没有理由让亨利活着
He has no reason to keep henry alive.
总统阁下  杰克·鲍尔在1号线
Jack bauer is on line one, madame president.
接进来
Put him through.
鲍尔先生  我是泰勒总统
Mr. bauer this is president taylor.
总统阁下  我们救出了您丈夫
Madame president,we have your husband.
他还活着
He is alive, but he sustained
但是他胸部中枪
A gunshot wound to the chest.
情况有多坏
How bad is it?
紧急营救小组已经稳定了情况
Emts are stabilizing him.
他们正准备把他送往
They're getting ready to transfer him
西阿林顿医院急救
To west arlington spital.
鲍尔先生  说具体点
Mr. bauer, be more specific.
我丈夫会没事吗
Is my husband going to be okay?
这要等见了医生才知道
We're not gonna know anything until the doctors see him.
阁下  我不得不告诉您  他失血严重
Ma'am,i have to warn you, he has lost a lot of blood.
杰克  我是比尔  你们抓到杜巴库了吗
Jack,it's bill. do you have baku?
没有  他在我们到之前就离开了
Negative-- he was gone before we got here.
总统阁下
Madame president,
既然您丈夫是杜巴库
Since your husband was the only leverage
留在这里的唯一筹码  那么
That dubaku had left, it's safe to say
他现在应该准备离开这个国家了
That he is trying to leave the country now.
你认为他下一步准备做什么呢
Have you any idea how he intends to do that?
我也不清楚  不幸的是
Not at this time. unfortunately,
他的人在这次行动中都死了
All his men were killed during the assault.
沃克探员和我将继续追踪
Agent walker and I will stay behind.
我们将搜索整个地区
We'll continue to search the area.
我们不得不假设杜巴库已经计划好了
We have to assume that dubaku has an exit strategy
撤退的方案
Already in place.
无论如何我们都要抓到他
Whatever we're going to do to find him,
而且必须要快
We're going to ha to do it fast.
是的
Yes.
谢谢你  鲍尔先生
Thank you,mr. bauer.
请随时通知我事情的进展
Please keep me apprised on everything.
好的  阁下
Yes,ma'am.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我很难过  总统阁下
I am so sorry,madame president.
伊桑  我要去医院
Ethan, I'm going to the hospital
陪我的丈夫
To be with my husband.
阁下  这恐怕不行
Ma'am,that's not possible.
您正在指挥一场军事行动
You're exeting a military invasion.
没有我在  将军们也能胜任这次行动
My generals can execute it perfectly well without me.
我们不能忽视
We can't ignore the fact
特勤局有内鬼的事实
The secret service has been compromised
我们无法保证您在
There's no way we can ensure your safety outside
-白宫外的安全  -我不在乎
the white house. I don't give a damn.
我不想在我丈夫生命垂危的时刻
I am not going to be held prisoner in this office
还把自己关在这间办公室里
while my husband is fighting for his life.
现在  要么找人
Now,either find some one
送我去医院  要么我自己开车去
To take me to the hospital or I'll drive there myself.
总统阁下  您了解我的工作履历
Madame president, you know my record of service.
如果您同意的话
If it's acceptable to you, I'm willing
我愿意担当您的保护工作
To assume responsibility for your security.
比尔  你已经不在职了
Bill,you're no longer credentialed.
你没有这个权限
You don't have the authority.
除非我们抓到杜巴库并审讯他
Until we capture dubaku and interrogate him,
不然我们根本不知道政府中还有谁
We have no idea who in the government is working
为他工作
For him.
您不知道可以信任谁
You do not know who you can trust.
但我可以信任你
But I can trust you.
是我告知了您这次危机
I brought this conspiracy to your attention,
总统阁下
Madame president.
我希望您能让我把它解决
I would hope that I could end it.
你需要我做什么
What do you need from me?
恢复我的职位和权限
Reinstate my government clearance,
允许我清查白宫全体官员
Allow me the authority to vet white house staff,
并让我的人进入联邦调查局
And allow to bring one of my people into fbi
给拉里·莫斯提供战术支持
To provide lary moss with tactical support.
你想带谁进入
Who is it that you want to bring in?
克罗伊·奥布赖恩
chole o'brian.
我可以保证  她是最佳人选
I can vouch for her; shs the best there is.
她的权限在反恐小组被解散时被收回了
Her clearances were also revoked when ctu was decommissioned.
除了她以外我们就没有
Isn't there anyone capable of handling these duties
别的人能胜任这项工作了吗
Without our having to reinstate her?
调查局里有人为杜巴库工作
Someone in the bureau is on dubaku's payroll.
除非我们找出这个人
Until we find out who it is,
否则拉里·莫斯是不会
Larry moss can't take the chance
冒险把他的人
Of bringing his own people
送去调查的
Into a manhunt for dubaku.
好吧
All right.
白宫特勤局的负责人是
The director of white house secret service operations
霍维斯探员
Is agent hovis.
我会命令他把安全协议转交给你
I'll order him to turn over security protocols to you.
我了解霍维斯  总统阁下
I know ted hovis, madame president.
他可不喜欢这样  他会给我们找麻烦
He's not gonna like this; he's gonna fight us.
考虑到他的手下要对
Well, considering that agents under his charge
我丈夫的事负全责
Are responsible for what happened to my husband,
我才不在乎他乐意与否
I don't give a damn what he likes.
布坎南先生  你要求你临危受命
You have your provisional appointment, mr. buchanan,
这是我的直接命令
Under the thority of this office.
谢谢您  总统阁下
Thank you,madame president.
送我到医院后再谢我吧
You can thank me by getting me to the hospital.
我马上安排
I'll make the arrangements.
总统阁下
Mame president...
我清楚你的想法  伊桑
Your concerns are clear to me,ethan,
但我意已决
But I've made my decision.
我只想干好我的工作
I'm only trying to do my job--
保护好您的利益
Looking out for your interests.
我当前的利益就是抓住杜巴库
My interest right now is catching ike dubaku.
他今天已经杀了无数的美国人
He has killed scores of americans today,
还想杀我的丈夫  而且还买通了我的人
He tried to kill my husband,and he has corrupted our government.
无论如何  我都要抓住这个狗东西
Whatever it takes, i want that son of a bitch found.
玛丽卡  玛丽卡
Marika... marika.
塞缪尔  你在这干吗
Samuel,what are you doing here?
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
好吧  我20分钟后休息
Uh, okay, well, I get a break in 20 minutes.
不行  就现在
No,now.
过来
come
好吧  出什么事了
Okay,what is it?
你吓着我了
You're scaring me.
出事了
Some thing has come up.
我必须离开这个国家
I need to leave the country.
什么
What?
什么时候
When?
马上
Right away.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你什么时候回来
When are you coming back?
玛丽卡  听我说
Marika, listen to me.
我对你说谎了
I haven't been entirely honest with you.
我的护照在几个月以前就过期了
My passport visa expired a couple months ago
我一直是非法居住在这里
And I've been in the country illegally.
恐怕移民局的人正在抓我
I'm afraid the immigration people have caught up with me.
是我姐姐干的  对吧
It was my sister,wasn't it?
她举报了你  是不是
She reported you,didn't she?
这已经不重要了
That doesn't matter now.
重要的是我必须在今晚离开这个国家
What is important is I have to leave the country tonight,
我想让你跟我一起走
And i want you to come with me.
今晚
Tonight?
玛丽卡  我们谈过这事
Marika,we've talked about this.
我向你承诺过有一天我会带你离开这
I promised you that one day I would take you away from here,
给与你应得的幸福
Give you the happiness that you deserve.
塞缪尔  我  我也想这样
Samuel, i-i want that,too,
但是今晚  有点太快了
But... but not tonight, not so soon.
玛丽卡  我已经没有时间和你争论了
Marika, i don't have time to argue with you!
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不能离开罗莎
I can't leave rosa.
她需要我  我是唯一能照顾她的人
She needs me; I'm the only one she has to take care of her.
你知道的
You know that.
我知道  我知道
I know,i know.
这就是她也要走的原因
Which is why she's going to join us.
和我们一起
Join us?
越快越好
As soon as possible.
今晚我只能弄到我们两人的票
I could only arrange tickets for both of us tonight,
但是我要你保证不告诉她
But I want you to promise not to tell your sister
我们的计划  至少现在不行
Of our plans, at least not yet.
我必须告诉她  我不能就这样一走了之
I have to; I can't just run off.
不  不行  她会给我们找麻烦
No,no,no,she might cause trouble for us,
我们就走不了了
Make it impossible for us to leave.
我保证你姐姐会在我们到后几天
I promise you your sister will join us
跟我们会合
Within a couple of days of our arrival.
-好吗  -我们去哪
Okay? our arrival where?
伯利兹城
Belize.
我给你看过我家在那的照片
I have shown you the photographs of my home there.
你爱我么
Do you love me?
你知道答案的
You know I do.
那就相信我
Then trust me.
说你会来
Say you'll come.
我去收拾行李
I'll get my things.
我还需要安排一下我们的行程
I still need to finalize our arrangements.
你回家去收拾东西吧
I want you to go home and pack.
等我电话
Wait for my call.
好的
All right.
-请讲  -是我
-Yes -It's me.
你都安排妥当了么
Have you made the preparations?
差不多了
Almost.
安排一条航道挺麻烦的
It's been tricky clearing a flight corridor
因为航管局还在禁飞
Since FAA still has most private
多数的私人和商务飞机
And commercial aircraft grounded
我相信你能搞定
I have faith you'll manage.
安排的是两个乘客吗
The arrangements are for two passengers?
按你的要求
Just as you requested.
你确定现在要走么  上校
Are you sure you want to leave now,colonel?
朱玛将军要是知道你放弃了任务
I can't imagine general Juma will be pleased
是绝对不会高兴的吧
To learn that you're abandoning your mission.
这次任务失败了
The mission is over.
该做的我都做了
I have done what I can do.
要是朱玛还不满意
If that is not enough for Juma,
那就让他见鬼去吧
Then to hell with him.
我已经拿到了你的护照和路线
I've got your passports and itinerary in hand.
半小时后老地方见
Meet me at our usual spot in half an hour.
我给你带去
I'll bring them.
不  咱们在罗斯福大陆酒店的
No,we'll meet in the lobby of the Roosevelt
大厅见面
Continental hotel.
这可不是什么好主意
That's not a good idea.
在这个时间  那人太多了
It'll be crowded there at this hour.
我知道
I know.
我要早点见你
I want the meeting earlier.
15分钟后见
I'll see you in 15 minutes.
开车
Go.
启动不了了
I can't get it to boot.
硬盘肯定被烧毁了
Hard drive must be fried.
该死
Damn it.
咱们搜下尸体
Let's search the bodies.
从他开始
Start with him.
喂
Yeah.
蕾妮  是我
Renee,it's me.
比尔·布坎南刚跟我通报了你们的情况
Bill buchanan just briefed me on your situation.
亨利·泰勒的情况如何
What's Henry Taylor's status?
他们把他送往
They've got him in an ambulance
西阿林顿医院了
En route to West Arlington Hospital.
我也不清楚他目前的情况
I don't know his current condition.
布坎南告诉我  你和鲍尔跟他们交火了
Buchanan told me you and Bauer were in a firefight.
是  我们打死了6个杜巴库的人
Yeah,we took down six of dubaku's men,
不过  杜巴库在我们来之前就离开了
But dubaku was gone before we got there.
你没事吧
You all right?
大风大浪都经历了
I've been in worse.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
小意思  我没事  拉里
I'm fine, Larry.
真的吗
Really?
我可不这么认为
I'm not so sure about that.
你什么意思
And what is that supposed to mean?
警方发给我一个报告
I'm looking at a report faxed to me from metro police.
一位叫卡罗尔·沃斯勒的太太声称
A mrs. carol vossler
一个不明身份的女人刚刚持枪
Is claiming an unidentified woman held her
劫持了她和她的孩子
And her child hostage at gunpoint.
她说那女人威胁要杀了她儿子
She says the woman threatened to kill her son.
拉里  你知道的
Larry,we discussed this.
我们得逼沃斯勒告诉我们
We needed to get vossler to tell us
泰勒被关押在哪
Where taylor was being held.
那是我们唯一的筹码
It was the only leverage we had.
对  没错  为达目的不择手段
Yeah, right, whatever's necessary.
杰克·鲍尔为他的野蛮行径
Jack Bauer's rationalization
做的合理化辩解
For every unethical action he takes.
我们达到目的了  拉里
It worked, larry.
难道不值这么做吗
Doesn't that count for something?
蕾妮  杰克·鲍尔就快被
Renee, Jack Bauer is about to be strung up
参议院处决了
By a senate subcommittee,
你正在步他的后尘
And you are following his playbook.
司法部办公室已经在调查
You already got the ag's office
你摘下坦纳呼吸器的事情
Looking into that thing you pulled
现在是一波未平一波又起
With tanner's respirator, and now this.
-又没有人受伤  -没人受伤
No one was actually hurt. no one...?
蕾妮  鲍尔杀了那女人的丈夫
Renee, Bauer killed the woman's husband!
蕾妮  我发誓
Renee, I swear to you,
你为你的处境很担忧
I am scared of what is happening to you.
你让这些人生不如死
You put these people through hell
你却对此心安理得
And it doesn't bother you.
我没有心安理得  拉里
I don't say that it doesn't bother me,larry.
我是说我们达到目的了
I said that it worked.
我当然也很难过
Of course it bothers me.
那女人的脸还在我眼前晃动
I can see that woman's face.
她和孩子用那种眼神看着我
She and her child staring at me with such...
她完全不知道自己的丈夫是个杀手
She had no idea that her husband was a killer,
是个叛国者
A traitor to his country,
我在她眼里就像一个恶魔
And she looked at me like i was the monster.
沃克探员
Agent walker.
等下
Hold on.
我对照了这些
I cross-referenced the information
掌上电脑的信息
On these PDAs.
发现一些银行交易记录
I came across some banking transactions.
所有相关的账户
All from a series of accounts
都是用一个地址注册的
Registered to the same address.
你觉得那是个安全屋吗
You think it's a safe house?
值得一查
It's worth a shot.
拉里  我们可能找到一个跟杜巴库有关的地址
Larry,we may have an address on dubaku.
欧几里德大街21917号
21917 Euclid Street.
6号公寓
Apartment six.
欧几里德大街21917号  6号公寓
21917 Euclid Street,Unit Six.
我们马上出发
We're moving out now.
你能提供卫星监控么
Can you provide sat surveillance?
好的  比尔·布坎南派人来做技术支持了
Yeah,bill buchanan's sending somebody over
但是在她来到并设置好之前
To run tech,but until she's up and running,
你们只能摸着石头过河了
You're gonna have to go in blind.
好的  保持联络
okay.We'll be in touch.
你没事吧
You sure you're okay?
没事
I'm fine.
我们走
Let's go.
联邦调查机构还在对发生在华盛顿
Federal investigations continue into the terrorist acts
及俄亥俄州汲沦谷的恐怖袭击
That have gripped the nation's capital,
进行调查
As well as the people of kidron,ohio.
尽管泰勒总统已经声明
Despite assurances by president taylor
-危机已经过去  -宝贝
In her national address that the threat has passed, hey,honey.
但从白宫得到的消息称
Sources at the white house will not confirm
还有部分主谋仍然逍遥法外
That all those responsible have been accounted for.
你确定不用我帮忙吗
Now,are you sure you're not gonna need my help?
我就是暂时参与下调查局的技术活
I'm just running FBI ops temporarily
等抓到杜巴库就没我的事了
Until they catch dubaku.
抓到他后  希望他能交出
Once they find him, hopefully he'll tell us
政府里所有为他工作的
The names of all the people
内鬼的名单
On his payroll that are inside our government.
那时我们就可以回家了
And then,we can go home?
没错
Then,we can go home.
小心点
Well,just be careful.
好吗
All right?
因为如果布坎南说得对
'cause if buchanan's right and dubaku
调查局有人为杜巴库工作
Has someone working inside the bureau...
我会小心的
I'll watch my back.
你照看好普雷斯科特
You just watch Prescott.
宝贝  妈妈要去上班了
Okay,sweetheart, mommy has to go to work.
要乖哦
You be good,okay?
妈妈  再见
Bye,mommy.
再见
Bye.
你也乖哦
You be good,too.
我会的
I will.
再见
Bye
如果遇到难题  记得联系我
And if you get all jammed up, you know where to find me.
请你交叉对照下我们和国土安全局的部署
I need you to cross-reference our deployments with homeland.
确保请求单号都能一一对应
Make sure the requisition numbers match up.
做完这些  你可以补做下
After that, you can catch up
-时间进度表  -开什么玩笑
On the hour list. Are you joking?
多麻烦啊   这么弱智的活儿
That is busy work, administrative crap
-你也分配给我做  -詹尼斯
You're handing me. janis...
我没时间也没兴趣
I don't have the time or the inclination
去跟你解释分配给你的任务
Right now to explain my assignments to you.
照做就是了
Just get it done.
莫斯探员  克罗伊·奥布赖恩
Agent moss,chloe o'brian just cleared security.
她上楼了
She's on her way up.
好的  谢谢
All right,thank you.
詹尼斯  在会议室开一个
Janis,set up a secure vpn socket.
安全虚拟专网端口
Port it to the conference room.
你要虚拟专网端口干嘛
Why do you need a vpn socket?
我从国土安全局找来个顾问
I'm bringing in a consultant from homeland
来检查CIP防火墙
To confirm there are no lingering gaps
有没有残留漏洞
In the cip firewall.
好了  拿到楼下去吧
That's fine. take that downstairs.
奥布赖恩女士  我是拉里·莫斯
Ms. o'brian,larry moss.
-欢迎来调查局  -你好
-Welcome to the fbi. -hi.
叫我克罗伊就好
You can call me chloe.
好的  这边请
All right,we're right in here.
布坎南说你已经了解情况了
Buchanan said you'd be up to speed.
是的
I'm up.
很好
Good.
沃克探员和鲍尔正在追查
Agent walker and bauer are pursuing
一个可能找到杜巴库的线索
A potential lead on dubaku.
他们在去这个地址的路上
They're en route to this address
在山悦区
In the mount pleasant district.
沃克探员请求卫星支持
Agent walker's requesting satellite support.
怎么了  有什么不对么
What's the matter? is something wrong?
我感觉有人在盯着我
I'm feeling a little exposed here.
如果外面有人为杜巴库工作
If someone out there is working for dubaku,
我们是不是该更隐蔽些呢
Shouldn't we be doing this more covertly?
目前为止  大家只知道
As far as anyone knows,
你是来梳理防火墙的
You're working on shoring up our firewall.
另外  也只剩下这个地方了
Besides,this is the only space available
在这  你可以访问我们所有的服务器
Where you'll have full access to our server.
我们的网络不支持远程访问
Our network doesn't port remote modules.
那效率多低啊
That's inefficient.
谁给你们建立的网络啊
Whoever set your network up that way
简直是外行
Didn't know what they were doing.
是我要那么设置的
I set our network up that way.
好吧
Okay
还有别的事情么
Something else?
你跟鲍尔工作很长时间了吧
You worked with bauer for a long time,didn't you?
7年了  时断时续
Seven years, on and off.
你能活到现在 还真是个奇迹啊
That's impressive. That you survived the experience.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
很多人都死了
Only that a lot of people didn't.
柯蒂斯·曼宁  瑞恩·查佩尔 他老婆
Curtis manning, ryan chapelle. His own wife.
你是说杰克老婆的死  是他的错么
Are you saying it's jack's fault his wife was killed?
你说呢
You tell me.
在我看来  杰克·鲍尔是最可靠
Jack bauer is the most trustworthy,
最值得尊敬的人  他还是我朋友
Honorable man I know, and he's my friend.
我劝你你还是少管闲事
Maybe you should worry less about him
多花点精力把你办公室
And more about the mole in your office
的内鬼找出来吧
Working for dubaku.
那是克罗伊·奥布赖恩吗
Is that chloe o'brian?
-在哪  -会议室里
- What?  - in the conference room.
克罗伊·奥布赖恩  她曾是反恐小组的
Chloe o'brian-- she was senior analyst
资深分析师
At ctu.
我上过她的课
I once took a seminar she gave.
她在这干嘛  -拉里说国土安全局派她过来
What's she doing here? larry said homeland sent her over
查下防火墙还有没有别的漏洞
To check for residual breaches from the firewall attack.
怎么了
what?
这不是她的专长啊
It just doesn't sound like her area of expertise.
另外  据我所知
Besides,as far as I know,
反恐小组解散后她就被解职了
She's been inactive since ctu was decommissioned.
你的护照和行程路线
Your passports and travel itinerary.
豪客西里748航班正在塔夫特机场加油
A hawker-siddley 748 is fueling at taft airfield.
半小时后起飞
Be ready to fly within a half hour,
它将带你去开曼群岛
Get you to the cayman islands.
从那到伯利兹城
You shouldn't have any trouble
应该没问题
Getting to belize from there.
我需要有人开车送我去机场
I need a car to the airfield and a driver.
你自己不是有车送吗
I assumed you had your own transportation.
不是我用
It's not for me.
明白了
I see.
是为那女孩准备的吧
It's for the girl
我不确定短时间内
Well, I'm not sure I can find
还可以找到可靠的人
Someone I trust on such short notice.
真的吗
Really?
吧台上的那个人
What about your man at the bar?
你说什么
Excuse me?
或者阳台上的两人之一
Or one of the two on the balcony watching now?
或者在那黑车里
Or the two in the black town car
等我出去的那两个
Waiting for me to leave?
你觉得我是傻子吗  伯内特先生
Do you think I am a fool, mr. burnett?
我知道你们现在当我是累赘
I know you people see me as a liability now.
这些人是来保护您的
These men are here to guarantee
上校  没别的意思
Your safety,colonel, not to threaten it.
保护我
Guarantee my safety.
真不错
How nice.
还故作真诚
And said with such sincerity.
你听好了
I want you to take this message back with you.
我离开这个国家时
If anything should happen to me
如果有什么意外发生
On my way out of the country--
事故或者蓄意谋杀
An accident or an assassination attempt,anything--
比如你慷慨捐赠的飞机
If the plane that you
爆炸了的话
Were so generous to donate decides to explode,
所有与我相关的人员和银行交易记录
A data file with all the names and bank transactions
都会被送到司法部查处
Of all those involved will be sent to the justice department.
完全没有这个必要
That is completely unnecessary.
上面所说一切
The same holds true
同样适用于玛丽卡·道诺索
If anything should happen to marika donoso.
我发誓  她对此事一无所知
I swear to you, she knows nothing of this.
她不会威胁到你们
She is no threat to you.
别忘了提醒你的司机
Make sure your driver knows this before he brings her to me.
明白我的意思吗
Do you understand what I am saying?
我需要一个肯定的答复
I want you to tell me that you understand
这样才能确保
What I am saying to you, so there
万无一失
Will be no mistakes.
明白了
I understand.
很好
Good.
伯纳特先生  同雇佣兵合作
The one thing I have learned
我学到一件事  就是他们
In the company of mercenaries, mr. burnett,is that ultimately,
只管自己的死活
They care about nothing but their own survival.
好运
Good day.
正如我所料
I was right.
杜巴库猜到我们要干掉他
Dubaku suspected we were gonna take him out,and apparently,
他收集了证据来保护自己
He assembled evidence to use as an insurance policy.
我们得让他顺利地离开
We need to make sure he gets out of the country
踏上逃亡之路
And safely into exile.
不然我们就完蛋了
Otherwise, we're all compromised.
我去做下安排
I'll make the calls.
你干嘛
What are you doing?
罗莎
Rosa.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
罗莎  听我说
Rosa,listen to me.
我们要离开这
We're going away from here.
我们所有人
All of us.
什么所有人
Well,what do you mean,all?
塞缪尔向我坦白了
Samuel told me the truth.
如你所料  他是非法移民
He's an illegal, just like you thought.
他必须得离开
He has to leave the country,
我同意和他一起走
And I've agreed to go with him.
你要离开我
You're leaving me?
不  只是分开一会  你也会过去的
No,no,only for a short time. you're gonna come,too.
塞缪尔都安排好了
Samuel's made plans.
我们会去
We're gonna live
伯利兹城和他一起住
With him in his home in belize.
玛丽卡
Marika...
他在向你撒谎
He's lying to you.
他没有
He's not.
我不会同意的
I won't let you do this!
天呐  罗莎
My god,rosa.
一直以来都是我在照顾你
I have taken care of you my entire life.
我为你牺牲了一切
I've sacrificed everything for you.
你为什么就不让我和他在一起
Why can't you let me have this?
我不相信他
I don't trust him.
任何喜欢我的男人
Oh,well, you never liked any man
你都不喜欢
Who's ever shown an interest in me.
每次我的幸福来临时
Every chance I've ever had at happiness,
你都会想方设法把它毁掉
You found some way of ruining it.
-这次不行  -玛丽卡
- But not this time.  - Marika,
我求你了  听我说
I'm begging you, listen to me.
-不  -玛丽卡  求你了
- No.  - Marika,please.
别走
Stop.
闪开
Move!
玛丽卡  求你了
Marika,please.
听我说  求你了  玛丽
Listen to me. I'm begging you,marik...
联邦调查局  不许动
Fbi-- don't move!
跪下
Get on your knees now!
On your knees!
你们两个  双手交叉
Both of you, put your hands
放到脑后
Behind your head, interlock your fingers.
现在
Now!
不许动
Do not move.
这安全了
We're clear.
杜巴库在哪
Where is dubaku?
-谁  -别和我耍花招
- Who?  - don't play games with me!
埃克·杜巴库  我们从银行账户追踪到这
Ike dubaku-- we traced bank accounts to this address.
他在哪
Now,where is he?
我们不知道你在说什么
We don't know who you're talking about.
我来帮你们回忆下
Let me make try and make this easier for you.
你认识他吗
You know this man?
不
No.
你撒谎
You're lying to me.
你为什么撒谎
Why are you lying to me?!
让我看看
Let me see.
就是他  我们认识
That's him-- we know him.
他称自己是安博 塞缪尔·安博
He calls himself aboa, samuel aboa.
-罗莎  闭嘴  -她正要去见他
- Rosa,shut up!  - she was going to meet him to leave me
你要去哪见他
Where were you gonna meet him?
你要去哪
Where were you going?!
我不清楚
I don't know.
-你怎么认识他的  你是他手下吗  -不
- How do you know him? you work for him?  - no.
-你是他手下吗 -不
- Do you work for him?  - no.
你知道他都干了些什么吗
You know what he's doing here in this country?
你知道
Do you have any idea...
他是个什么样的人吗
What this man is?
他是我的一切
He's everything to me.
-你是  -米切尔
- Nurse...?  - mitchell.
米切尔护士  我想见下我丈夫
Nurse mitchell,i'd like to see my husband.
女士  我...
Uh,ma'am,i...
我不知道行不行
I don't know if that's possible.
我听说由舒尔曼医生主刀
I was told that dr. schulman will be doing the surgery.
他在哪里
Where is he?
打扰了  总统阁下
Excuse me, madame president.
我是李·舒尔曼  您丈夫的主治医生
I'm lee schulman, your husband's surgeon.
跟我来  我带您见他
If you come with me, you can see him now,
但时间不宜过长
But you'll need to keep it brief.
谢谢
Thank you.
您应该知道泰勒先生至少要
You should know that mr. taylor's looking
做5个小时的手术
At a minum of five hours in surgery.
子弹划破他的肺动脉
The bullet lacerated his pulmonary artery
留在他的胸椎下部
And lodged in his thoracic region.
他还伴随大量的内出血
He's also suffered massive internal bleeding.
能告之预测的情况吗
Can you offer any kind of prognosis?
我是直肠子  舒尔曼医生
I'm a blunt woman,dr. schulman.
请您直说吧
I appreciates bluntness.
前景不是很乐观
His chances aren't good ma'am.
但我会全力以赴的
But I'll do everything I can.
请允许我
If you'll excuse me.
去准备手术
I need to scrub up now.
斯肯菲尔德医生  请去305房间
Dr. schoenfeld,305.
亨利  亲爱的  你听得到吗
Henry darling, can you hear me?
艾莉
Ally.
是的  亲爱的
Yes, sweetheart.
我在这
I'm here.
我很后悔  对罗杰的死因  我没有听你的
I'm so sorry I didn't listen to you about roger.
你是对的
You were right.
他没有自杀
It wasn't suicide.
现在我知道了
I Know that now.
你一直是对的
You were always right.
他是个英雄
He was a hero.
是的
Yes.
他是  你也是
He was,and so are you.
抱歉  总统阁下
I'm sorry, madame president,
手术要开始了
But the anesthesiologist is ready now.
布坎南先生
Mr. buanan?
在  总统阁下
Yes,madam president
我需要你帮我做件事
There's something I need you to do for me.
找到我女儿奥利维亚  把她带来
Have someone find my daughter olivia and bring her to me.
您还没告诉她吗
Have you had a chance to tell her?
我们有一段时间没联系了  布坎南先生
My daughter and I haven't spoken for some time,mr. buchanan.
她不接我电话
She'd never get on the phone with me.
她在一家咨询公司上班
She works for a consulting firm--
叫马特林·诺里斯
Martling norris.
能派个信得过的人去吗
Do have someone trustworthy you can send?
没问题
Yes,ma'.
我可以办到
I believe I do.
这里也是他
And here he is again
穿着总统护卫的服装
In the uniform of the presidential guard
在臭名昭著的穆卡图监狱门外
At the gates of the notorious mukatu prison.
还有这  在足球场里
And here, inside the soccer stadium
在巴拉卡尔大屠杀后
After the barakar massacre.
他从此获得
The event that earned him the nickname
"桑加拉屠夫"的称号
The butcher of sangala.
行了  够了
Oh,please. no more.
能再说下他的真名吗
What did you say his real name was again?
杜马库
Dubaku.
埃克·杜巴库
Ike Dubaku.
我亲眼见到他的所做所为
I have seen first hand what he's capable of.
几个月前我在非洲
I was in africa a few months ago.
他还杀了我一个朋友
He was responsible for murdering a friend of mine.
上帝啊
Oh,god.
我知道这很让人震惊
I know this is a shock.
抱歉
And I'm sorry.
真的很抱歉
I really am.
可现在的情况是这样
But here's the situation.
我们现在就需要你帮助
We need your help, and we need it now.
怎么帮
What kind of help?
我们要在这个人逃出国前
We need to put this man in custody
把他抓住
Before he can leave the country.
她已经告诉你了
Well,she already told you.
她不知道他在哪里
She doesn't know where he is.
对  可你之前说过
Yeah,but you said earlier
你要去见他  在哪里
That you were going to meet him. where?
他没说
He didn't say.
他只告诉我回家收拾行李等他电话
Just told me to go home and pack and wait for his call.
把你电话给我
Give me your phone.
干吗
Why?
要是他打来  你接电话
When he calls, I want you to answer it.
不  不  不
No. no,no.
-不行  -你行的
I can't. I can't. yes,you can.
听我说
Listen to me. just...
你听我说
Just-just listen to me.
都过去了
It's-it's over.
你曾经认识的那个男人
The man you thought you knew,
你以前喜欢的那个男人
The man you had feelings for--
他不存在
He doesn't exist.
他只给你留下了
All you've been left with
谎言和背叛
Are his lies and his betrayal.
是他吗
Is that him?
玛丽卡  拜托
Marika,please.
你只需要接电话
All I want you to do is answer the phone
跟他谈话  这样我们就能
And talk to him so that we can find out
知道他想与你在哪里见面
Where he wants to meet you.
拜托  你做得到
Please. you can do this.
试试看好吗
Please just try.
喂
Hello.
玛丽卡
Marika?
是我
Yes.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
没事
I'm fine.
怎么这么长时间才接电话
What took you so long to answer the phone?
我在卧室打包行李呢
I was in the bedroom packing.
你在哪
Where are you?
怎么了
What's wrong?
你的声音有点不对劲
You sound strange.
是罗莎
It's... it was rosa.
我打包时被她发现  我们吵了一架
She caught me packing, and we argued.
她会找我们的麻烦吗
Is she going to a problem for us?
不会
No.
抱歉  塞缪尔
I'm sorry,samuel.
我只好告诉她一切
I had tell her everything.
只能这样
It was the only way.
她现在理解了
But,uh... but she understands now.
你确定吗
Are you certain?
嗯  她没事了
Ah. yeah, she's fine.
现在他已经理解我们只是 暂时分开
Now that she knows she and I will be together again In a few days.
她应该感谢上帝给了
Hmm. she should thank heaven
她一个这么好的妹妹
She has such an angel for a sister.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready to go?
快了
Almost.
那你抓紧吧
Hurry up then.
我派了辆车去接你
I've had a car sent for you.
应该很快就到
It should be there very shortly.
下楼等车吧
Go downstairs and wait for it.
这辆车要带我去哪里
Where is it taking me?
别担心  司机知道
Don't worry. the driver will know.
我只想要我的爱人
I just want the woman I love
尽快下楼
To get downstairs as quickly possible.
好吧
Okay.
没事了
It's all right. it's all right.
你做的很好
You did great.
知道接头地点了吗
Did we get the rendezvous point?
没有  他派司机开车过来
No. he's sending a car with a driver.
过来
Come here.
现在街上还没有人
There's no one on the street yet.
我们可以抓住司机
We could grab the driver,
让他供出杜巴库的位置
Get him to tell us dubaku's location.
我们不能保证司机会开口
There's no guarantee we can get him to talk.
要是花的时间太长
And if we take too long,dubaku's not gonna
-杜巴库就溜了  -那我们该怎么做
Wait around. so then what do we do?
我们可以让她与他见面
We can get her to go meet with him.
-什么  -我们可以追踪她
What? we could track her.
用她的手机当发射器
We could use her cell phone as a transponder.
你想把这姑娘送到杜巴库那去吗
You want to send that girl to dubaku?
我们别无选择
We don't have another choice.
-杰克  -想抓住杜巴库
Jack. you want to get dubaku,
这就是我们的机会
This is our shot.
玛丽卡
Marika?
我想请你帮个忙
I have a favor to ask of you.
我们不会强迫你这么做
We can't make you do this.
不过车来的时候  我们想让你和司机走
But when the car arrives, we would like you to go
那样我们就能跟着你找到杜巴库
With the driver so that we could follow you back to dubaku.
什么意思
Oh,what-what are you talking about?
你想让她去他那里和他见面吗
You want her to go to him and face him?
这是能抓到他的
It's the only chance we have of finding him before
-唯一机会了  -我去
He disappears forever. I'll do it.
不
No!
我是你姐
I'm your older sister,
我不准你去
And I won't allow it.
这事由不得你  罗莎
It's not your decision to make,rosa.
是我自己的决定
It's mine.
难道这么做不对吗
Ain't it the right thing to do.
把你手机给我
Let me see your phone.
你要做什么
What are you doing?
查看你的安全码
Getting your sid number.
这样我们就能追踪到你
It's how we're going to track you.
你不是孤身一人去那
You're not gonna be out there alone.
沃克探员和我都会跟着你
Agent walker and I will be following you.
我们会在你身后一里内
We'll never be more than a mile behind.
一旦你到达目的地
As soon as you reach the destination--
我们就出击
That's when we'll move in.
玛丽卡
Marika.
一里  你疯了吗
A mile! are you crazy?
罗莎  够了
Rosa,enough.
你听到他说的话了
You heard what he said.
他是个杀人恶魔
He's a murderer!
-他会伤害你  -他不会
He could hurt you. he won't.
罗莎  我本该听你的话
Rosa, i should have listened to you.
亲爱的
Sweetheart.
你曾警告过我的
You warned me about him.
听着  我之所以那么说
Listen,the only reason
是因为我很嫉妒
Why I said those things was because I was jealous.
我不想失去你
And I didn't want to lose you.
拉里  我是杰克
Larry,it's jack.
蕾妮说有人在做战术支持  是吧
Renee said you had someone running operations support?
是的  她在这里
Yeah. she's right here.
我把免提打开了
I'll put you on speaker.
杰克  我是克洛伊
Jack,it's chloe.
需要什么
What do you need?
要用多久才能为
How long's it gonna take you
一部手机建立一个卫星信标
To set up a sat beacon for a mobile line?
一般几秒钟就行
Usually a few seconds,
可在他们的这种落后的系统上
But with the backward way they have the system set up,
至少要几分钟
It's gonna take at least a few minutes.
好吧  我把安全码告诉你
Okay,well,let me give you the sid number.
1-c-4-8-6-8-9.
收到没有
You got it?
收到
Got it.
杰克  你在追踪谁
Jack,who are you tracking?
与杜巴库有染的一个女人
A woman who's involved with dubaku.
他正派车来接她
He's sending a car to take her to him.
她是他的手下吗
She's one of his operatives?
不是
No.
比那复杂的多
It's-it's more complicated than that.
亚瑟  你不会再找到一家公司
Arthur,you're not going to find another firm
能为像你这样小型的药品公司
That's done more high-level consulting work
做如此高级的咨询了
For a relatively small pharmaceutical company like yours.
我的公司曾替州长制定计划
Remember,my firm helped the governor craft a plan
在他最后的预算改革中
To swap property taxes for sales taxes
用消费税替换财产税
In his last budget reform.
你可别说没给戴克斯特·卡尔省下大笔钞票
Tell me that didn't save dexter-carr a bundle.
确实如此  奥利维亚
Oh,it did,olivia.
可鉴于我要雇的人是你
But since I'm specifically looking to hire you,
我就要知道你能做什么
I need to know what you yourself can do.
你需要我做什么
Whatever you need.
你看过我履历  知道我的成就
You know my accomplishments, yove seen my resume.
我是指你的家庭背景
I mean white house influence.
在白宫的影响力
Considering your family.
我们不是说客  亚瑟
We're not lobbyists,arthur.
合同里写的明明白白
It states that clearly in the contract.
我只是觉得你能和总统美言几句
I just thought,since you had the president's ear...
不能
I don't.
这有关系吗
Is that going to be a problem?
打扰了  泰勒小姐吗
Excuse me,ms. taylor?
我们认识吗
Do I know you?
我叫亚伦·皮尔斯
My name is aaron pierce.
你办公室的人告诉我你在这
your office told me you would be here
总统派我来找您
I've been dispatched at the request of the president.
你的证件上写着
Your credentials
你已经退休了  皮尔斯先生
You've retired, mr. pierce.
或许没人通知您
Perhaps no one informed you
几个月前  我拒绝了特勤局的保护
I refused secret service protection months ago.
这我知道  女士
I'm aware of that,ma'am.
可现在情况特殊
This is a special circumstance.
你也看到了  我现在有点忙
Well,as you can see,i'm a little busy right now.
现在不合适
This isn't a good time.
抱歉  可我必须这样
I'm sorry,but I have to insist.
-真的  没关系  -不
-It's really... it's all right. -no.
不  不行
No,it's not all right.
我妈有什么重要的事
What is it that's so impornt
非要在做生意的时候找我
For my mother to steal me away while I'm trying to do business?
这我不便透露  女士
I'm not at liberty to say,ma'am.
事关机密
That information is confidential.
奥利维亚  我们可以以后再谈
Olivia,we can pick this up at a later time.
亚瑟  等等
Arthur,wait...
保持联络
We'll be in touch.
女士  请
Ma'am,please?
除非你告诉我什么事
I'm not going anywhere with you
否则我不会和你走
Until you tell me what this is about.
是你父亲  泰勒小姐
'sour father,ms. taylor.
他中枪了
He's been shot.
现正在西阿灵顿医院做手术
He's in surgery at west arlington hospital.
你母亲也在那里
Your mother's there now.
这些都没对外公布
None of this is public knowledge.
上帝啊  我
My god,i...
我的车就在外面
My car is just outside.
打扰一下  西恩
Excuse me,sean.
能把服务器的数字测试密钥借我吗
Can I please get the digital beta key for the server?
做什么
Why?
拉里要的
Larry asked for it.
是防火墙评测之类的事
Something to do with the firewall assessment
要是拉里想要  为什么不直接找我
If larry wants it, why doesn't he come to me?
不知道
I don't know.
-不如我去问他  -不
Maybe I ought to go ask him. no.
好吧
Okay.
我觉得拉里把克洛伊·奥布莱恩
I think that larry brought in this woman,
这女人带来顶替我
Chloe o'brian,to replace me.
我只想知道 他们在干什么
And I just want to get a bead On what they're working on.
-仅此而已  -仅此而已吗
That's all. that's all?
说不定我们会丢掉饭碗
That's enough to lose us both our jobs.
我看我还是别包庇你了
Well,maybe I should stop covering for you.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
艾丽卡
Erika
还有你这个要性不要命的家伙
And you,and your little sexual indiscretions.
这些事我都没和拉里还有你太太说过
I've said nothing to larry or your wife.
你也不想我这么做吧
I'm sure you'd like me to keep it that way.
知道吗  你是个小贱人
You're a little bitch, you know that?
你是个小贱男
You're a little bitch.
杰克  已建立连接  收到信号
Okay,jack. the link's up, I've got the signal.
收到  我再打给你
Copy that. I'll get back to you.
开始行动
We're on.
玛丽卡
Marika...
我们得走了
We got to go.
没事的
It's all right.
你
You--
联邦调查局的
Fbi.
要保证她的安全  听到了吗
You keep her safe,you hear me?
我们会的
We will.
我好害怕
I'm really scared.
你不会有事
You're going to be fine.
记住  我们就在你身后
Just remember, we're right behind you.
在这里等着
Move up here.
听着  如果遇到麻烦
Now,listen, if you get into trouble,
-就播1-0  -不
You can signal us by dialing one-zero... no.
不  不要那样做
No,i don'want you to do that.
不要做任何事
Don't do anything that's going to raise
-否则司机会起疑  -好的
The suspicion of the driver. okay.
准备好了吗
You ready?
嗯  好了
I'm ready. yeah.
-好  -好
Okay. okay.
好
Okay.
你这是干什么
What the hell are you doing?
她很害怕
She was scared.
我只想让她知道除我们外
I wanted her to know there was another option
她还有别的选择
Than waiting for us to swoop in.
如果想找到杜巴库  就别无选择
If we're going to find dubaku, there are no other options,
明白吗
You understand?
拜托  你也指挥过这样的行动
Come on,you've run operations like this.
这次完全没有战术支持
Not without full tactical support,
至少要有两组人作为后背增援
And at least two backup units on the scene.
她没有丝毫保障  杰克  我不赞成
She's naked out there,jack. I don't like it.
这事由不得你
This isn't about you.
这是她和杜巴库的事
This is about her and dubaku
听着  世事无常
Listen,life gets ugly,
好人没好报  这就是现实
Innocent people get hurt-- that's a reality.
至少她选择参与这件事
At least she got to make a choice
做正确的事
To be involved, to do the right thing.
单就这点
Which is a lot more
就比杜巴库其他的帮凶强
Than I can say for dubaku's other victims.
我们只有一个任务  就是找到杜巴库
We have one job here-- that's to get dubaku.
其他的事  不要多想
Outside of that don't get involved.
克洛伊  车到了
Chloe, the car's here.
收到
Copy that.
她上车了
She's getting in the car.
收到
Copy.
她离开了
She's moving.
锁定他们了吗
Are you locked in?
嗯  他们由14街向南行驶
Yeah,i've got them heading south on 14th.
能把追踪图像传到
Can you upload the tracking grid
沃克探员的PDA上吗
To agent walker's pda?
不行  我会指示你们
No,i'll have to direct you.
-跟紧点  -明白
Just keep us close. Understood.
由14街向右转
Head towards 14th, make a right.
收到
Copy that.
还有多远
How much further?
继续向西行进  穿过罕布什尔大街
Continuing west on our street, crossing hampshire avenue.
你与目标不到一里远
You're less than a mile behind the target car.
收到
Copy that.
目标转弯
Target car is turning,
前往康涅狄格
Left on connecticut.
好  在杜邦转盘环岛
Okay,rounding dupont circle.
莫斯探员  目标的北方区域
Agent moss,is there anything in the northern quad of the grid
是否有可以起飞的地方
That would indicate where dubaku can hide a plane
不
No.
不确定
Nothing definitive.
有很多可以起飞的地点
Could be any number of launch sites.
啊
Whoa! whoa! whoa!
怎么回事  出什么事了
What was it? what happened?
杰克  我们有麻烦
Jack,we've got a problem.
什么事  克洛伊
Chloe,what's wrong?
刚失去追踪图像
We just lost the tracking grid.
-什么  -我也不清楚
What?! i-i don't know.
突然断线
It just suddenly glitched out.
千万不能跟丢了
We can't afford to lose them.
杰克  我发誓要保证她的安全
Jack,i gave this woman my word we'd protect her.
我知道  克洛伊  重新连接
I know. chloe,get it back up.
我们在尽全力  杰克
We're doing our best, here,jack.
等等
Wait.
连接恢复
It's back up.
怎么回事
What the hell happened?
不知道  我正在运行诊断程序
I don't know,i'm running a diagnostic right now.
杰克  他们由马萨诸塞大街
Jack,they're moving southeast
向东南方向行驶
On massachusetts avenue.
你与目标只有半里远
You've closed the gap to about a half mile.
最好后撤些
You may want to back off a little bit.
好  收到
Okay, copy that.
不好
Oh,no.
怎么
What?
刚才有人在监视系统
Somebody was in the system.
什么  什么意思
What? what are you talking about?
这间办公室里的某人
I'm saying someone in this office
刚刚映像了我的终端
Was mirroring my terminal.
他一定知道了我们在做什么
Whoever it was knows exactly what we were doing.
能进行反追踪吗
Can you backtrace the breach?
不行  对方切断了连接
No. the link was severed.
可能来自任何地方
It could have come from anywhere.
杰克  你听到了吗
Jack, you getting this?
看来我们可能有安全漏洞
It looks like we might have a security breach.
有人刚刚监视了我们的通讯
Someone is mirroring our comm.
杰克  到处都是警察
Jack, they're coming from all sides.
拉里  我们这里也有情况
Larry,we got a situation here.
什么事
what's going on?
警察在拦我们的车
I got Metro PDs trying to build a roadblock around us.
什么
What?
他们为什么这么做
Why would they be doing that?
不知道  帮我甩掉他们
I don't know. just get 'em off us!
拉里  想想办法
Larry,do something!
我是莫斯探员
This is agent moss.
给我接市警总局
Connect me with metro district command.
举起手  举起手
Hands in the air! hands in the air!
我叫杰克·鲍尔
My name is jack bauer,
与我随行的是
My passenger
一名联邦探员
Is a federal agent.
立即下车
Get out of he car right now!
-联邦探员  -趴下
Federal agent! On the ground!
她是联邦探员
She's a federal agent!
先生  把手放在身后
Put your hands behind your back,sir.
拉里  快想想办法
Come on,larry,do something!
警长  我要你立即释放这些人
Captain,you've got to release these people immediately!
不  不  肯定是误会
No. no,that is a mistake
我们没对他们发布拘捕令
No federal warrants have been issued for them!
不  发过
Yes,they have.
有份拘捕令要求追捕那辆车
A warrant was called in for the vehicle.
车上人员持有枪械  属危险人物
"occupants armed and dangerous,
需采取必要手段进行抓捕
To be apprehended with decisive force."
谁批准的
Issued by whom?
调查局  没有授权  不过识别码正确
FBI, this office, there is no authorization, But the routing code's real.
肯定是这的人做的
This was definitely done by someone here.
玛丽卡的车向东上了N大街
Marika's car just turned east onto n street.
警长  听好
Captain,listen carelly.
我是负责这次行动的联邦探员
I'm the special agent in charge of this operation,
这份拘捕令现在立即作废
And I am revoking these warrants immediately.
不行
No.
我没时间去层层汇报
No,i don't have time to deal with our chain of command.
我要你立即放人
You need to release these people right now!
谢谢
Hey. thank you.
奥布莱恩要顶替你吗
So is o'brian here to replace you?
不知道  不是吧
I don't know. no.
拉里在让她与杰克·鲍尔
Larry's using her for some kind of
进行秘密行动
Covert operation with jack bauer.
他们在追踪前往杜巴库那里的车辆
They're tracking a car to dubaku.
为什么不让我们知道这些事
Why would he keep us in the dark about something
不知道
Like that? I don't know.
不知道  可我不喜欢这样
I don't know, but I don't like it.
我搞定了鲍尔和沃克
Hey, i took care of bauer and walker.
他们已经被扣住了
They're pinned down.
为什么现在才告诉我
Why am I being brought in on this so last minute?
莫斯正在独自指挥这次行动
Moss is running this op on his own.
我好不容易
It took me some time
才窃听到他的电话
To tap into his phone line.
他在和警署通话
He's on with metro right now.
你能切断他们的
Can you at least disable the tracking signal
追踪信号吗
They're using to follow the girl?
不行  在我这里不行
No,not from my console.
不过从频率上来看
But judging by the frequency,they're using
他们正用她的手机来追踪她
Her cell as the tracker.
好的
All right.
干得好
Good work.
你说过一旦杜巴库达到目的
You told me that once dubaku served his purpose,
你就会把他干掉
You'd take him out.
为什么还在帮他
Why are we still helping him?
他威胁说会利用手中的名单
He's threatening to expose us using the database he's kept
和相关账户举报我们
With nes and accounts of everyone involved.
包括我吗
Including mine?
谁都跑不掉
I mean,everyone.
我们不知道文件在哪
We don't know where the file is,
所以只能祈祷他能得偿所愿
So you just get pray that he gets away.
对  与今早的
Yes,it has to do with the terrorist threats
恐怖袭击有关
That happened this morning.
喂
Hello?
你有麻烦了
You got a problem.
什么事
What is it?
调查局已经招降了你女友
Your girlfriend's been turned by the fbi.
我不信
I don't believe you.
他们在半小时前和她见面
They met with her half hour ago,
告诉了她  你的真面目
Told her who you really are.
不可能
That's impossible.
玛丽卡不会这么做
Marika would never do this.
是局里的内线亲口告诉我的
I got it from our source inside the bureau,
不会有错
It is definite.
她答应带他们去你那
She agreed to lead them to you,
利用她手机作为跟踪器
Using her cell phone as a tracker.
我的内线已经设法
Look,my source managed
暂时干扰了他们的监控
To stall their surveillance team for a while,
不过你得立即去机场
But you need to get to the airfield immediately.
我给司机打电话
I'll call my driver,
让他干掉她
Have him take care of her.
不  交给我
No. I'll do it.
上校  我说了  他们在跟踪她
Colonel, i told you, they are tracking her.
如果你让她来找你
If you let her come to you,
你可能就走不掉了
You're risking your chances of escape.
我说了  我要亲自处理她
I said,i'll take care of her!